<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basic on Welcome! A place where ancient architecture &#39;Vastu&#39; meets modern Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning!</title>
    <link>https://vastu.io/categories/basic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basic on Welcome! A place where ancient architecture &#39;Vastu&#39; meets modern Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Vastu.io; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vastu.io/categories/basic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>16 Directions or 32 Directions?</title>
      <link>https://vastu.io/blog/2015/10/10/directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vastu.io/blog/2015/10/10/directions/</guid>
      <description>Most important aspect of Vastu Directions Directions are the most important aspect of Vastu. Each direction presents opportunity for either spiritual, economic, social or in some other form.
There are primary 4 directions: North, South, East and West &amp;ndash; called cardinal directions, while there are sub-directions such as: North East, South East, North West, South West. Each sub-directions get their fair share such as &amp;ndash; North-NorthEast(NNE), North-NorthWest(NNW), East-NorthEast(ENE), East-SouthEast(ESE), South-SouthEast(SSE), South-SouthWest (SSW), West-NorthWest(WNW), North-NorthWest(NNW)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vastu Principles</title>
      <link>https://vastu.io/blog/2015/10/10/vastu-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vastu.io/blog/2015/10/10/vastu-principles/</guid>
      <description>Principles of Vastu The principles of Vastu had been explained in ancient Hindu scriptures, called Puranas, including Skanda Purana, Agni Purana, Garuda Purana, Vishnu Purana, Bruhatsamhita, Kasyapa Shilpa, Agama Sastra and Viswakarma Vastushastra.
The fundamental premise of Vastu rests on the assumption that the earth is a living organism, out of which other living creatures and organic forms emerge, and so every particle on earth and space possesses live energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Vastu?</title>
      <link>https://vastu.io/blog/2015/10/10/what-is-vastu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vastu.io/blog/2015/10/10/what-is-vastu/</guid>
      <description>Vastu Shastra Vastu Shastra is a traditional concept in Hindu system of architecture, which translates to &amp;lsquo;science of architecture&amp;rsquo;. It is an ancient Indian science developed thousands of years ago by Indian sages. According to Viswakarma - an architect who is considered the creator of Vastu described Vastu as a science complete in itself.
Vastu Shastra is the ancient Indian science of architecture, which governs town planning and designing of man-made structures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>